export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which record label is synonymous with organizing major hardstyle events such as Defqon.1 ?",
        option1: "Armada Music",
        option2: "Q-Dance",
        option3: "Monstercat",
        option4: "Spinnin Records",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What country is often associated with the origins and popularization of hardstyle music ?",
        option1: "Netherlands",
        option2: "Germany",
        option3: "United States",
        option4: "India",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the typical BPM (beats per minute) range of hardstyle music ?",
        option1: "110-130 BPM",
        option2: "140-160 BPM",
        option3: "170-190 BPM",
        option4: "200-220 BPM",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which musical element distinguishes hardstyle from other electronic dance genres ?",
        option1: "Heavy bass drops",
        option2: "Complex melodies",
        option3: "Distorted kicks",
        option4: "Vocal chops",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these festivals is renowned for showcasing hardstyle music and culture ?",
        option1: "Tomorrowland",
        option2: "Ultra Music Festival",
        option3: "Electric Daisy Carnival (EDC)",
        option4: "Qlimax",
        ans: 4, 
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the hardstyle DJ who founded the record label Dirty Workz ?",
        option1: "Headhunterz",
        option2: "Brennan Heart",
        option3: "Coone",
        option4: "Phuture Noize",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which hardstyle DJ recently retired at Defqon1 2023 Closing Ceremony ?",
        option1: "The Prophet",
        option2: "Alpha2",
        option3: "Pavo",
        option4: "Luna",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the signature dance move associated with hardstyle music events ?",
        option1: "Shuffling",
        option2: "Freestyle",
        option3: "Dougie",
        option4: "Jumpstyle",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which hardstyle festival was discontinued after the year 2022 ?",
        option1: "Qapital",
        option2: "Q-Base",
        option3: "InQontrol",
        option4: "ImpaQt",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Blademasterz is an alias of which hardstyle DJ ?",
        option1: "D-Block & S-Te-Fan",
        option2: "Brennan Heart",
        option3: "B-Front",
        option4: "Ran-D",
        ans: 2,
    }
];